Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Public Affairs Department Records 1945-2000 (bulk 1959-1996) MS 3009-RG 19
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Vice President Donald Wilson Files, 1960-1994; 1968-1989; 62.5 Linear feet in 63 record cartons
  - Corporate: Foreign Policy Association Meeting, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1647, Folder 13-14)
  - Corporate Identity Study: Siegel & Gale, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1647, Folder 15-19)
  - Corporate Identity Study: Siegel & Gale, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 1-6)
  - Corporate Identity Study: Siegel & Gale [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Corporate Image, 1985 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Image and Communications, 1969-1976 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 8)
  - Corporate Investor Factbook, 1985 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 9)
  - Corporate Investor Relations, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 10)
  - Corporate: Levin Appointment, 1988 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 11)
  - Corporate Logos, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 12-13)
  - Corporate: Luncheon with Dow Jones and Company Executives, 1980 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 14)
  - Corporate: Magazine Reorganization, 1987 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 15)
  - Corporate: Magazine Reorganization [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Corporate: Management Changes, 1986 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 16)
  - Corporate Management Committee: Luncheons, 1985 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 17)
  - Corporate: Meetings with Glenn Britt and Urban "Pete" Uelbelhoer, 1986 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 18)
    At this time, Uebelhoer is the Time Inc. Treasurer and Britt is CFO of HBO.
  - Corporate Memberships, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 19)
  - Corporate: New Objectives and Strategies for Time Inc. Booklet, 1982 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 20)
  - Corporate: 1984 United States Exhibition in Beijing, China, 1982 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 21)
  - Corporate: Officers Possibly Serving on Non-Profit Organization Boards, 1988 (Offsite-box 1648, Folder 22)
  - Corporate: ORC Executive Caravan Survey, 1984 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 1)
  - Corporate: Organization Consultants, Inc., 1984 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 2)
  - Corporate: Overhead Summary, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 3)
  - Corporate: Overhead Task Force, 1988 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 4)
  - Corporate: Pay Increase Limits for Executives, 1978 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Presentation: Ford, Enfield "Flicky", 1979 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 6)
  - Corporate: Q&As on Davidson Retirement Package, 1987 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 7)
  - Corporate: Reception for New Management, 1980 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 8)
  - Corporate: Restatement of Policy on Corporate Conduct, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 9)
  - Corporate: Retirement for Larsen and Donovan, 1979 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 10)
  - Corporate: Role of Editor-in-Chief, 1979 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 11)
  - Corporate: Scott, Foresman and Company, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 12)
  - Corporate: Senior Management: Appointment, 1980 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 13)
  - Corporate: Senior Management: Meetings, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 14-18)
  - Corporate: Spin-Off Forest Products, 1983 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 19-20)
  - Corporate: Staff Reductions, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1649, Folder 21-23)
  - Corporate: Stock: Tender Offer, 1979 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 1)
  - Corporate: Stockholder Rights Plan and Sale of American Television and Communications Inc. (ATC) Stock, 1986 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 2)
  - Corporate: Stockholder Rights Plan and Sale of American Television and Communications Inc. (ATC) Stock [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Corporate Strategy: General, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 3-5)
  - Corporate: Strategy Book, undated (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 6)
  - Corporate: Sullivan Principles, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 7-9)
  - Corporate: Sullivan Principles [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Corporate: Surveillance of Americans Abroad, 1979 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 10)
  - Corporate: Takeover, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 11-12)
  - Corporate: Takeover Language, 1986 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 13)
  - Corporate: Time Inc. Audiences, 1981 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 14)
  - Corporate: Time Inc. Booklet, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 15)
  - Corporate: Time Inc. 60th Anniversary, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 16-18)
  - Corporate Training Program, 1982 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 19)
  - Corporate: Trip: Lyford Cay: Executive Dialogue, 1985 (Offsite-box 1650, Folder 20-21)
  - Corporate: United Nations Ambassadors Meetings, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 1)
  - Corporate: Write Down (Job Cuts), 1987 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 2)
  - Cost Cutting Questions and Answers, 1986 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 3)
  - Davidson, Ralph: Candidate for Special Assistant [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Offsite-box R24)
  - Dayton Hudson Corporation: Corporate Public Involvement, 1983 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 4-5)
  - Department Head Directory, 1985 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 6)
  - Dinner for Donovan, Grunwald and Graves, 1979 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 7)
  - Discover: General, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 8)
  - Discover: Sale, 1987 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 9-10)
  - Eastex Inc.: Big Thicket National Preserve: General, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 11-14)
  - Eastex Inc.: Big Thicket National Preserve: House Hearings, 1973 (Offsite-box 1651, Folder 15-18)
  - Eastex Inc.: Clips, 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 1-2)
  - Economic Development Council On-Loan Executive Program, 1982 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 3)
  - Education Commission of the States Meeting, 1983 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Committee for American Trade (ECAT), 1974-1982 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 5)
  - Energy Conference: Nassau, Bahamas, 1973 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 6)
  - Energy Conference: Williamsburg, VA, 1974 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 7-10)
  - EPCOT Center: General, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 11)
    Time Inc. was invited to build an exhibit in the CommuniCore of Future World for the opening of this new Disney themepark. Though the records include extensive planning materials, Time Inc. ultimately did not complete the exhibit.
  - EPCOT Center: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - EPCOT Center: Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R24)
  - EPCOT Center: Brochures, Drawings, Articles, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 12-15)
  - EPCOT Center: CommuniCore Exhibit Preliminary Concepts, 1981 (Offsite-box 1652, Folder 16)
  - EPCOT Center: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 1-3)
  - EPCOT Center: First Working Proposal, 1980 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 4)
  - EPCOT Center: Future Choice Pavilion Concept and Design, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 5)
  - EPCOT Center: Marketing Conference, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 6)
  - EPCOT Center: Meeting, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 7)
  - EPCOT Center: Memorandum to Board of Directors, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 8)
  - EPCOT Center: MetaForm Incorporated, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 9)
  - EPCOT Center: Participants' Conference, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 10-11)
  - EPCOT Center: Promotion Reports, 1981 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 12-13)
  - ESOP, 1987 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 14)
  - Eureka College, 1984 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 15)
    Contains records on the first presentation by the Time Distinguished Speakers Program.
  - European Management Forum, 1982 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 16)
  - Executive Briefing Lunches, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1653, Folder 17)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 1)
    Regarding Paid-During-Service subscription selling operation.
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and Ervin Committee, 1971-1977 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 2-4)
    Includes transcripts of Chairman Andrew Heiskell's statements to the Senate Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights along with transcripts of non-Time Inc. representatives.
  - Financial Conference, 1986 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 5)
  - Five Year Plan Presentation, 1978 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 6)
  - For the Record (Corporate Public Affairs Newsletter), 1986 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 8)
  - Ford, Enfield "Flicky": Retirement Lunch, 1984 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: General, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: Corporate Communications Conferences, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 11-17)
  - Fortune: Education Summit, 1988 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: Survey, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1654, Folder 19)
  - 42nd Street Development Project, 1984 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 1)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Centennial Celebration, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 2)
  - Free Admission Programs, 1976-1981 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 3)
  - Freedom of the Press, 1973 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of the Press [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - FTC Media Symposium, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 5)
  - FYI: Correspondence and Issues, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 6-12)
  - FYI: Interview with Dick Munro, 1983 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 13)
  - FYI: Story on Roy E. Larsen, 1979 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 14-15)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape.
  - Government Activities, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 16)
  - Grunwald, Henry: Retirement: Publisher Letter, 1987 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 17)
  - Hammer, Michael: Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 18-19)
  - Heiskell, Andrew: Retirement Parties and Speeches, 1980 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 20-22)
  - Heiskell, Andrew: Trip to Africa, 1981 (Offsite-box 2094, Folder 23)
  - Hemisphere Club Memberships, 1976-1983 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 1)
  - Hiland, Bruce: Memoranda, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 2-5)
  - Home Box Office (HBO): General, 1982-1988 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 6-14)
  - Home Box Office (HBO): Frank Biondi and Michael Fuchs Personnel Change Announcement, 1984 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 15)
  - Home Box Office (HBO): Incorporated into Time Inc. Orbit, 1983 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 16)
  - Home Box Office (HBO): Sex and Violent on Television, 1984 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 17)
  - Hotel Rooms (Trade Arrangements), 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 1655, Folder 18)
  - Howard Hughes Manuscript: Correspondence, 1972 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 1-3)
    1 audiocassette (Soundesign C-60): analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Wilson-Hannah Jan 6, 1971 11:30PM."
  - Howard Hughes Manuscript: Press Releases and Q&A, 1972 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 4)
  - Howard University Reception, 1985 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 5)
  - Hughes Aircraft: Time Pay Television Project, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 6-7)
    Includes records on national satellite programming and networking.
  - IBM Technical Support, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 8)
  - Inaugurations: 1980 and 1988, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 9-11)
  - Inauguration: 1980 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Information Systems Department, 1980 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 12)
  - Inland Container Corporation: General, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 13-14)
  - Inland Container Corporation: Class Action suit, 1978 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 15)
  - Inland Container Corporation Merger, 1978 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 16)
  - Inside Time Inc., 1984 (Offsite-box 2095, Folder 17-18)
    Inside Time Inc. is a quarterly corporate magazine for employees. Records include planning documents and issues.
  - Inside Time Inc., 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 1-10)
  - Internal Communications Campaign, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 11)
  - Internal Distribution, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 12)
  - International Center of Photography (ICP), 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 13)
  - International Institute of Communications, 1980 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 14)
  - Iran, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 15-16)
  - Jessup, John Knox: Book, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 1957, Folder 1-5)
    Includes thank-you letters to Henry Grunwald from recipients of complimentary copies of the book.
  - Kekst and Company, 1984 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 17)
  - Kerr, Jeanne: 25th Anniversary Luncheon, 1984 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 18)
  - Khrushchev Remembers: Book and Tapes to Columbia University, 1974 (Offsite-box 1656, Folder 19-20)
  - Khrushchev Remembers: Book and Tapes to Columbia University, 1974 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 1-2)
  - Koch, Ed: Luncheon, 1988 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 3)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: General, 1986 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 4-5)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Analysis of Legal Coverage: Out Card, undated (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 6)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Analysis of Media Coverage, 1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 7)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Brill Correspondence, 1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 8)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Brill Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 9)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Court Documents and Records, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 10-13)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Court Documents and Records [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Daily Legal Testimony [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Dassi Wagner Contract and Fees, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 14)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Grunwald Staff Memorandum, 1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 15)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Libel Suit Research, 1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 16)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Op Ed Pieces, 1984 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 17)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Press Releases, 1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 18)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Q&As, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1657, Folder 19)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Settlements [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Time Statements, 1985 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 1)
  - Legal: Sharon v. Time: Weekly Clips, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 2-3)
  - Legal: Subpoenas and Other Matters [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Offsite-box R24)
  - Legal: Subpoenas and Other Matters [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Legal: Time Inc. Policy, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 4)
  - Leisure, 1986 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 5)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 6)
  - Levin, Gerald: Appointment Announcement, 1986 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 7)
  - Liability Insurance Coverage, 1988 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 8)
  - Life: General, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 9)
  - Life: Background Information, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 10-11)
  - Life: Circulation Reduction and Demise of Life International, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 12)
  - Life: Demise Announcement, 1972 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 13-16)
  - Life: Franklin Delano Roosevelt Exhibition, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 17)
  - Life In the 60s Exhibition, 1988 (Offsite-box 1658, Folder 18)
  - Life: Khrushchev Remembers, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 1-4)
  - Life: Monthly, 1978 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 5)
  - Life: Photography Contests/Bicentennial, 1971 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 6)
  - Life: Suspension, 1972 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 7)
  - Lighthouse for the Blind, 1986 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 8)
  - Linen, James: Memorial Service, 1988 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 9)
  - Literacy: General, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 10-12)
    Includes records on Time Inc.'s involvement in various literacy education and promotion projects and a publication of a literacy booklet.
  - Literacy: McKinsey & Co., 1988 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 13-14)
  - Literacy: Time Inc. Social Platform, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 15-16)
  - Little, Brown: General, 1987 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 17)
  - Little, Brown: 150th Anniversary, 1986 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 18)
  - Los Angeles Times: Clips and Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1659, Folder 19)
  - Luce, Henry, III: Retirement, 1980 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 1)
  - Lyndhurst Data Center Closing, 1987 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 2)
  - Luftman, Michael: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 3)
  - Lunchtime Forumes, 1987 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 4)
  - Magazine Development Group, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 5)
  - Magazine Group Identity: Siegel & Gale, 1988 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 6)
  - Magazine Group Reconstruction, 1985 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 7-8)
  - Magazine Issues (Magazine Group Newsletter), 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 9-10)
  - Magazine Newsletter of Research, 1977 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 11)
  - Magazine Publishers Association (MPA): Political Action Committee, 1977-1987 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 12-17)
  - Magazines: Advertising and Circulation Figures, 1987 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 18)
  - Magazines: Fact Sheet, 1987 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 19)
  - Magazines: Separate Magazine Corporation, 1988 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 20)
  - Manhattan Cable, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 21)
  - Manhattan Cable and Queens, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 22)
  - March of Time, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 23)
  - Matching Grants, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 24-26)
  - McCall's and Working Woman, 1986 (Offsite-box 1660, Folder 27)
  - McKeough and Nicholas Staff Announcement, 1982 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 1)
  - Media and Business, 1977 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 2)
  - Media and Society Seminars, 1982 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda to the Staff: General, 1969-1979 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 4-6)
    These folders contain bound volumes of memoranda sent to all staff and collected by Wilson.
  - Memoranda to the Staff: General, 1983-1989 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 1-5)
  - Memoranda to the Staff: Personnel, 1969-1982 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 7-9)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art: Henry Kissinger Book, undated (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art: Paper Conservation Proposal, 1980 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art: Show, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art: Treasures from the Kremlin, undated (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 13)
  - Minority Business Development, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: General, 1985 (Offsite-box 1661, Folder 15-16)
    Includes a memoranda from Wilson stating it is Time Inc.'s new stationary style, probably created after the logo redesign.
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: General, 1985 (Offsite-box 2050, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: General, 1986 (Offsite-box 2050, Folder 2-4)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: General, 1987 (Offsite-box 2050, Folder 5-7)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: General, 1988 (Offsite-box 2050, Folder 8-10)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Brack, Reginald, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 2050, Folder 11-12)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Davidson, Ralph, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2050, Folder 13-16)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Davidson, Ralph, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 1665, Folder 1-7)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Grunwald, Henry, 1987 (Offsite-box 1665, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Levin, Gerald, 1984 (Offsite-box 1665, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Levin, Gerald, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1665, Folder 10-14)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: McManus, Jason, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1665, Folder 15-16)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Munro, J. Richard, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1665, Folder 17-18)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Munro, J. Richard, 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 1662)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Munro, J. Richard, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 2051, Folder 1-5)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Letters: Nicholas, N. J., 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 2051, Folder 6-8)
  - Miscellaneous Requests, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2051, Folder 9-15)
  - Miscellaneous Requests, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 1663)
  - Miscellaneous Requests, 1988 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 1-3)
  - Money, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 4)
  - Morfogen Associates (Consultant for cultural affairs), 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 5-7)
  - Munro, J. Richard: Letter to Staff (Company Updates), 1984 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 9)
  - Munro, J. Richard: Meeting (with Staff), 1984 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 10)
  - Munro, J. Richard: Memorandum from Luftman on Major Events Since Munro Became CEO, 1985 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 11)
  - Munro, J. Richard: New Year Letter: 1985, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 12)
  - Munro, J. Richard: Non-Executive Briefing Lunch, 1984 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 13)
  - Munro, J. Richard: Strategy and Budget Presentation Meetings, 1986 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 14-16)
  - Munro, J. Richard: 30th Anniversary Party, 1987 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 17)
  - Munro, J. Richard: Trip to Vassar (Executives in Residence Program), 1983 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 18)
  - National Democratic Convention, 1980 (Offsite-box 1664, Folder 16)
  - National News Council, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 1-2)
  - National Newspaper Association Conventions, 1976-1985 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 3-15)
  - National Security Directive Statement by Ralph Davidson, 1983 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 16)
  - Nature Conservancy: Roy E. Larsen Sandyland Sanctuary Ceremony, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 17-18)
  - New York City: Regional Plan Association: Citizens Mobilization Board, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Guild: General, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 20-21)
    Includes issues of the newsletter On Time.
  - Newspaper Guild: Strike, 1976 (Offsite-box 1957, Folder 6-7)
  - Newspaper Subscriptions, 1987 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 22)
  - Newstours: Middle East, 1975 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 23-24)
  - Newstours: Africa/Middle East, 1978 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 1-5)
  - Newstours: Mexico, 1979 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 6)
  - Newstours: 1981 (Eastern Europe, Russia, Middle East) (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 7-9)
  - Newstours: Mexico, 1983 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 10)
  - Newstours: Pacific Rim, 1985 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 11-14)
  - Newstours: Pacific Rim, 1985 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 1-6)
  - Newstours: USSR (Soviet Union), 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 7)
  - New York Festival, 1981 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 8)
  - New York Perspectives Meetings, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 9-11)
  - New York Public Library, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 12)
  - New York State Bonus Tax Bill, 1978 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 13)
  - Nicholas, N. J.: Breakfast Meetings, 1988 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 14)
  - Non-Executive Briefing Lunches, 1985 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 15)
  - Non-Financial Goals Determined by Munro, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear Weapons and Atlantic Alliance, 1982 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 17)
  - Office Relocation of Wilson, 1987 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 18)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1982 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 19)
  - Olympics, 1984 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 20)
  - Paddle Tennis Courts, 1976 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 21)
  - Parenting, 1986 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 22)
  - Patterson, Martha Priddy: Correspondence on Tax Legislation, 1986 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 23-25)
  - People, 1979-1988 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 26)
  - Personnel: General, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 27-29)
  - Personnel: General, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 1)
  - Personnel: Anderson, Lem [RESTRICTED], 1977-1984 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Campbell, Ron [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Employee Benefits, 1986 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 2)